你好
Hello!
我是博士
I'm the Doctor.
现在 很多人问我
Now, a lot of people have asked me,
我是怎么让自己看起来这么酷的
how I managed to look so cool.
嗯 其实并不是很多人
Well, not...not actually a lot of people
他们用的也不是"酷"这个词
and they didn't use the word "cool"
也不是任何其他词语
or any of the other words.
因为从来没有人问过我这个问题
Because no one's ever asked me that at all.
但如果他们问我
But if they had asked me.
我会用一个字来回答
I'd have answered with one word,
我的衣服
My clothes.
尤其是领结和有时会戴的毡帽
Especially the bow-tie and a fez sometimes,
公平地说 这不是一个字
which in fairness is several words.
但这是因为我很激动
but that's because I'm excited.
是的 很激动
Yes, excited!
今天 为了"帮助儿童"特别节目
Today, for Children in Need,
我要送出我身上的衣服
I am giving the clothes off my back!
我的夹克
My jacket.
全宇宙独一无二
Unique in the universe.
由无限多的粗花呢制成
Made of infinity tweed.
如果这件夹克被任何子弹或激光击中
If this jacket is hit by any kind of bullet or laser beam
甚至是被三重折叠的量子强化忍者武器击中
or even a triple enfolded quantum strengthened ninja staff
那它就彻底毁了
It would be completely ruined.
所以请对它小心点
So please be careful with it.
我的领结
My bow-tie.
领结现在是 将来也一直是很酷的
Bow-ties are and always will be cool.
我的衬衫
My shirt.
看起来像一件普通的衬衫
Looks like an ordinary shirt,
摸起来像一件普通的衬衫
feels like an ordinary shirt,
其实就是
is in fact,
一件普通的衬衫
an ordinary shirt.
我的裤子
My trousers.
不是普通的裤子
Not just any old trousers.
超级裤子
Hyper trousers!
与普通裤子非常相似
Very similar to normal trousers,
但是名字里面有个"超级"
but with word hyper in front.
我的靴子
My boots.
一只
One.
两只
Two.
三只!
Three!
噢 时间领主
Oh! Time Lords.
我们总是充满惊喜
We are full of surprises.
现在
Now,
如果你们中有谁想要竞标
if any of you would like to bid for
这些完全独一无二的衣服
these completely unique items of clothing,
链接正在显示在你的屏幕上
the URL is appearing on your screens right now.
不 不 别担心 这些不是真的衣服
No, no. Don't worry, these aren't my real clothes.
这些是全息影像衣服
These are hologram clothes.
请不要碰遥控器上的红色按钮
Please don't touch the red button on your remote,
否则它们会消失的
or they might just disappear.
啊 不! 住手!
Ah, no! Stop that!
住手!
Stop it!
好的 朋友们 我需要转移一下注意力
Okay guys, I'm going to need a diversion.
快放预告片!
Run the trailer!
英国 1941年
England, 1941.
战争正在打响
And there's a war on.
这里闹鬼吗
Is it haunted?
你是谁?
Who are you?
通常被叫做"博士"
Usually call the Doctor,
或者"管理员"
or the Caretaker,
或者"滚出这个星球"
or get off this planet
那个人简直太荒唐了
That man is quit ridiculous!
我知道!
I know!
离他远点
Stay away from him.
为什么你房间里放了个电话亭
Why we got a phone box in your room?
这不是电话亭 这是我的衣柜
It's not a phone box, it's my wardrobe.
你弟弟他在哪
Your brother, where is he?
好的 来吧
Okay, Come on.
我们在哪里
Where are we?
在客厅里的盒子里的森林里
In forest in a box in a sitting room.
现在的学校都是怎么教你们的
What do they teach you in school these days?
这片森林十分不对劲
There is something very wrong in this forest.
而你弟弟现在正在森林中间呢
And your brother is right in the middle of it.
史上最棒的圣诞节
Best Christmas ever!
我知道
I know.